<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple Computer//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
    <dict>
	<key>version</key>
	<string>2.1</string>
	<key>file</key>
	<string>Cyberduck-2.1.dmg</string>
	<key>comment</key>
        <string>Changelog:
2.2b1
- Keychain integration (Saving passwords)
- New file transfer manager
- Full Unicode support
- Support for public key authentication (SSH)
- Live filtering directory listings
- Improved Rendezvous support (jmDNS 0.2)
- Reorder bookmarks with drag and drop
- Drag files from the browser to the transfer manager
- Drag links to the transfer manager to start download
- Browser can be customized to show/hide certain columns
- Japanese Localization
- Italian Localization
- Portuguese Localization
- Spanish Localization
- Various improvements and bug fixes

2.1
- Bookmarks can now be edited
- Bookmarks can now be saved as a regular file (Drag the bookmarks to the Finder)
- Bookmarks saved as files can be imported by dropping them on the Bookmarks Drawer
- Double clicking a Cyberduck bookmark file in the Finder will open a new browser and connect to the remote site
- Bookmarks can now be modified
- Specify an initial directory upon new connection (e.g. public_html instead of the default home)
- Use keyboard shortcut (commann-up/down) for browsing a directory
- Uploaded files have the same permissions as locally
- Updated icon set
- Remembering sort order while browsing
- Toolbar icon to toggle Bookmark drawer
- Updated SSH Core (v0.2.5)
- Dutch Localization
- German Localization
- Smaller changes and bug fixes

2.1b5
- HTTP is now supported again. Files can be downloaded from regular web servers
- Cyberduck can now be configured as the default FTP helper application. See "http://www.monkeyfood.com/software/moreInternet/". This seems to work with Safari and Internet Explorer
- Dragging files to the Finder is now more reliable
- The transfer panel does now close again if defined so in the preferences
- The buffer size (the size of download chunks to keep in memory before writing to disk) is now adjustable
- Login to anonymous FTP servers where no password is needed is now supported
- Smaller bug fixes

2.1b4
- Cyberduck now has the official creator code 'CYCK' and can handle URL events from other applications. See "http://www.monkeyfood.com/software/moreInternet/" to configure Cyberduck as the default FTP helper application
- Smaller bug fixes

2.1b3
- Localization support
- Files and foldes can now be dragged to the Finder to download them
- Windows do now no more stack exactly on the top of prior one
- There are now equivalent menu actions for the toolbar items
- Modification dates and time are now displayed correctly
- The modification date column is now sorted correctly
- Browser columns are now sortable in both directions
- When deleting multiple files and directores, the file list will now only get updated at the end because of performance
- If multiples have been selected to transfer, Cyberduck now puts them in the same queue and opens only one connection to the server
- There is a new command 'Go to folder' for changing the working directory quickly
- Many smaller bug fixes

2.1b2
- SSH (SFTP) support
- Completly rewritten user interface using the Cocoa Framework
        </string>
    </dict>
</plist>